http://www.gfbf.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy • Georgia Firefighters Burn Foundation
Our ProgramsBurn SurvivorsGFBF TalksBelli Memorial Endowment and ScholarshipCamps & RetreatsFire ServiceChesney Fallen Firefighters Memorial GrantFirefighter Recognition LuncheonFirefighter SupportProject R.E.A.C.H.Give Burns The BootCampaign InformationHistory
About UsContact UsFinancialsOur MissionOur TeamBoard of DirectorsStaffResourcesEvent CalendarJoin Our Mailing ListNewslettersDonateOur ProgramsBurn SurvivorsGFBF TalksBelli Memorial Endowment and ScholarshipCamps & RetreatsFire ServiceChesney Fallen Firefighters Memorial GrantFirefighter Recognition LuncheonFirefighter SupportProject R.E.A.C.H.Give Burns The BootCampaign InformationHistoryAbout UsContact UsFinancialsOur MissionOur TeamBoard of DirectorsStaffResourcesEvent CalendarJoin Our Mailing ListNewslettersDonatePrivacy PolicyWE’RE COMMITTED TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACYYour privacy matters to the Georgia Firefighters Burn Foundation. This notice is provided to better protect your privacy through explaining our online information practices. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website. Please note that this policy is subject to change.INFORMATION WE COLLECTOn some pages, you can sign up for our email list, submit forms for volunteering, contact or program consideration, make donations, and register to attend events.Following are the types of personal information we may collect on these pages:Name Email address Phone number Address Profession Payment Information (for donations) Date of BirthWhen you use the public areas of our website, you are doing so anonymously.THE WAY WE USE INFORMATIONWe collect aggregate use information, such as the number of hits per page, for internal and marketing use only; we do not provide your personally identifying information to the public. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.DONOR PRIVACYIn accordance with our privacy policy, we will not share or sell a donor’s personal information (Name, Email address, Phone number, Address, Profession, Payment Information and/or Date of Birth) with anyone else nor send donor mailings on behalf of any other organization. We will only share personal information once a donor has given Georgia Firefighters Burn Foundation permission to do so.CONTACT US Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please call us at (404) 320-6223 or write an email to mbailey@gfbf.org.Georgia Firefighters Burn Foundation is a 501(c)(3)      Privacy Policy      Edit Site      Email      Contact Us      Join Our Mailing List
Site by All Terrain Studios      ©2020
